molecularstation.com 2010-12-22

# Privacy Policy Molecular Station

Bookmark / Share This Science Site   

Molecular Station understands your privacy and will not sell or give this information to outside sources.

Molecular Station collects personal information about you only when you specifically and knowingly provide it to us, such as forum and blog registration purposes. 

This personal information that you provide to Molecular Station will not be made available to third parties outside of Molecular Station without your explicit permission. Your personal information will be used to personalize and enhance your experience with Molecular Station.

### The Use of Cookies

Cookies are data which a web site transfers to an individual's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can enhance the web by making it more useful by storing your preferences for a particular site. The use of cookies is an internet and industry standard, and many if not most major web sites use them to provide enhanced features for their users. 

Molecular Station has two primary uses for its cookies. We use them primarily to specify your unique preferences, and to make it easier for you to use our forum and other registration areas. Secondly, we use cookies to track user trends and patterns on Molecular Station. This enables us to better understand and improve areas of Molecular Station Service. While these activities depend on the use of a "cookie," visitors to Molecular Station always have the option of disabling cookies through their internet browser preferences or options.  Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You either can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or indicate when a cookie is being sent, or block cookies from Molecular Station. However, some Molecular Station Services such as our forum may not function properly if you refuse cookies. 

### External Links and Links to other Sites and Servers 

Molecular Station contains many links to other sites. Those sites may not have the same privacy standards as Molecular Station. These sites may send their own cookies to users, and consequently collect personal information and data that Molecular Station would not. 

Users should be aware that when you are on Molecular Station, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from Molecular Station pages that take you outside our service. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. Take note and caution when proceeding to other sites.

Molecular Station's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond Molecular Station's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. 

### Science News

Stress can enhance ordinary, unrelated memories, a team of neuroscientists has found in a study of laboratory rats. Their results, which appear in the journal PLoS Biology, may bolster our understanding of post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD) and c...

CHICAGO --- Busy doctors can miss important details about a patient's care during an office examination. To prevent that, Northwestern Medicine researchers have created a whip-smart assistant for physicians ? a new system using electronic health rec...

* [ ACS applauds Congress for passing American competitiveness bill](http://www.molecularstation.com/science-news/2010/12/acs-applauds-congress-for-passing-american-competitiveness-bill/)

WASHINGTON, Dec. 21, 2010 ? The American Chemical Society (ACS) applauds Congress for reauthorizing the America COMPETES Act today. America COMPETES (Creating Opportunities to Meaningfully Promote Excellence in Technology, Education and Science), ...

* [ The Science Coalition lauds House, Senate passage of America COMPETES](http://www.molecularstation.com/science-news/2010/12/the-science-coalition-lauds-house-senate-passage-of-america-competes-2/)

Washington, DC ? The Science Coalition issued the following statement today from President Deborah Altenburg after the U.S. House of Representatives passed H.R. 5116, the America COMPETES Reauthorization Act of 2010: On behalf of The Science Coali...

* [ The Science Coalition lauds House, Senate passage of America COMPETES](http://www.molecularstation.com/science-news/2010/12/the-science-coalition-lauds-house-senate-passage-of-america-competes/)

Washington, DC ? The Science Coalition issued the following statement today from President Deborah Altenburg after the U.S. House of Representatives passed H.R. 5116, the America COMPETES Reauthorization Act of 2010: On behalf of The Science Coali...

* [ New evidence of stem cells? pivotal role in cancer shown in Stanford study](http://www.molecularstation.com/science-news/2010/12/new-evidence-of-stem-cells-pivotal-role-in-cancer-shown-in-stanford-study/)

STANFORD, Calif. ? Leukemia patients whose cancers express higher levels of genes associated with cancer stem cells have a significantly poorer prognosis than patients with lower levels of the genes, say researchers at the Stanford University School ...

* [ New evidence of stem cells? pivotal role in cancer shown in Stanford study](http://www.molecularstation.com/science-news/2010/12/new-evidence-of-stem-cells-pivotal-role-in-cancer-shown-in-stanford-study/)

STANFORD, Calif. ? Leukemia patients whose cancers express higher levels of genes associated with cancer stem cells have a significantly poorer prognosis than patients with lower levels of the genes, say researchers at the Stanford University School ...

* [ Gene alteration identified that predisposes to syndrome with high risk of cancer](http://www.molecularstation.com/science-news/2010/12/gene-alteration-identified-that-predisposes-to-syndrome-with-high-risk-of-cancer/)

Researchers have identified a new genetic alteration that predisposes individuals to Cowden syndrome, a rare disorder that is characterized by high risks of breast, thyroid and other cancers, according to preliminary research published in the Decemb...

* [ Activity of certain stem cell genes linked with worse outcomes in acute myelo...](http://www.molecularstation.com/science-news/2010/12/activity-of-certain-stem-cell-genes-linked-with-worse-outcomes-in-acute-myeloid-leukemia-patients/)

In an examination of leukemic stem cells (LSC), researchers have found that patients with acute myeloid leukemia who had higher activity of certain LSC genes had worse overall, event-free and relapse-free survival, according to a study in the Decemb...

Contrary to the belief of many scientists (as well as many members of the public), new research confirms that Africa has two?not one?species of elephant. Scientists from Harvard Medical School, the University of Illino...

For more click here:[Science News](http://www.molecularstation.com/science-news/)
